Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.13
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; XIII.
  - Attorney General Thornburgh's Files, 5.
    - Nuggets" Files
      - Communications with persons represented by legal counsel, memoranda from Attorney General Thornburgh to DOJ litigators (aka Thornburgh Memorandum), and other related articles continuing past Thornburgh's AG years, June 8, 1989-2001 (Box 778, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence from Attorney General Thornburgh to President Bush, 1990-1991 (Box 778, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence from Attorney General Thornburgh to Vice President Quayle and members of Congress, 1990-1991 (Box 778, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence to Attorney General Thornburgh from various persons, organizations and cabinet staff, 1989-1991 (Box 778, Folder 31)
      - Crime: The Attorney General's Crime Summit including remarks by Attorney General Thornburgh and others, March 4-5, 1991 (Box 778, Folder 32)
      - Crime: Crime bill and remarks of President Bush in announcement of bill, March 11, 1991 (Box 778, Folder 33)
      - Department of Justice: administrative memoranda, news clippings, and correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 778, Folder 34)
      - Department of Justice: publications and reports regarding various topics (including Attorney General's Semiannual Management Report to Congress), April-September, 1990 (Box 779, Folder 1)
      - Drug testing: court cases and rulings, 1965-1987 (Box 779, Folder 2)
      - Drug testing: news clippings and memoranda, 1989-1991 (Box 779, Folder 3)
      - Drug testing: Supreme Court case American Federation of Government Employees v. Burnley, October, 1988-April, 1989 (Box 779, Folder 4)
      - Historical articles regarding the Attorney General position, the Department of Justice, Supreme Court, and administration of justice, 1982-1991 (Box 779, Folder 5)
      - Independent Counsel issue and appointment of special independent counsel for criminal investigations of members of Congress, 1988-1989 (Box 779, Folder 6)
      - Iran Contra affair: memorandum from James Reynolds, chief of Terrorism and Violent Crime Section of DOJ Criminal Division, to Robert Mueller, III, Assistant Attorney General, August 2, 1991 (Box 779, Folder 7)
      - Law Enforcement Coordinating Committee (LECC): reports and memoranda, 1989-1991 (Box 779, Folder 8)
      - Legislative and administrative policy initiatives for the Department of Justice: memorandum to AG Thornburgh from Thomas Boyd, director of the OPD, April 21, 1989 (Box 779, Folder 9)
      - Media guidelines for the availability of information to the media: memoranda to AG Thornburgh from David Runkel, director for communications, February-December, 1990 (Box 779, Folder 10)
      - Memoranda to and from Department of Justice employees (excluding AG Thornburgh), 1989-1991 (Box 779, Folder 11)
      - Memoranda from AG Thornburgh to Department of Justice employees on various issues, 1990-1991 (Box 779, Folder 12)
      - Memoranda to and from Department of Justice employees, including AG Thornburgh, 1990-1991 (Box 779, Folder 13)
      - Memoranda to AG Thornburgh from Department of Justice employees and letters from Thornburgh to legislators, 1989-1990 (Box 779, Folder 14)
      - Memoranda to AG Thornburgh from Department of Justice and White House staff, 1990-1991 (Box 779, Folder 15)
      - News clippings, memoranda and notes on topics of interest, 1989-1991 (Box 779, Folder 16)
      - News releases, 1989-1991 (Box 780, Folder 1)
      - Notes and to-do lists kept by Thornburgh, 1989-1991 (Box 780, Folder 2)
      - Opportunity action plan to civic and charitable organizations (including President Bush's remarks in announcement of plan), February 27, 1991 (Box 780, Folder 3)
      - Organization and operation of the Office of Attorney General (OAG) and future tasks: memoranda to AG Thornburgh from Rick Stafford (RAS) and Mark Richard, 1988-1990 (Box 780, Folder 4)
      - "Operation Rescue," Wichita abortion protest, August-September, 1991 (Box 780, Folder 5)
      - Rule of Law delegation: report on trip to Romania (Thornburgh not part of trip), 1991 (Box 780, Folder 6)
      - S & L fraud: "Attacking Financial Institution fraud: A Report to the Congress of the United States", 1990-1991 (Box 780, Folder 7)
      - S & L fraud: Correspondence between Thornburgh and Senators and news release regarding financial institution fraud asset recovery, 1990-1991 (Box 780, Folder 8)
      - S & L fraud: Fraud section, Bank of Credit and Commerce International (BCCI) investigation and prosecution of BCCI's bank takeover scheme in the United States, 1991 (Box 780, Folder 9)
      - S & L fraud: statistics and fraud initiatives, June-August, 1990 (Box 780, Folder 10)
      - S & L fraud: House of Representatives Banking, Finance & Urban Affairs, includes "Fraud in Financial Institutions: U.S. Attorney's Report", April, 1990 (Box 780, Folder 11)
      - S & L fraud: House of Representatives member concerns and documents, 1990 (Box 780, Folder 12)
      - S & L fraud: Housing and Urban Development (HUD), prosecution against, 1989-1990 (Box 780, Folder 13)
      - S & L fraud: indictments and convictions, December, 1990-July, 1991 (Box 780, Folder 14)
      - S & L fraud: legislation regarding financial institutions fraud passed by the Senate, July 11, 1990 (Box 780, Folder 15)
      - S & L fraud: news clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 780, Folder 16)
      - S & L fraud: news releases, February-September, 1990 (Box 780, Folder 17)
      - S & L fraud: procurement fraud, 1989-1990 (Box 781, Folder 1)
      - S & L fraud: prosecution updates from the Department of Justice (DOJ), October 1, 1988-August 12, 1991 (Box 781, Folder 2)
      - S & L fraud: securities fraud news clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 781, Folder 3)
      - S & L fraud: Securities and Loan Task Force, July, 1989 (Box 781, Folder 4)
      - S & L fraud: Senate members concerns and Senate Banking Committee hearings, 1990 (Box 781, Folder 5)
      - S & L fraud: speeches by Department of Justice officials (not AG Thornburgh), February-July, 1990 (Box 781, Folder 6)
      - S & L fraud: survey results and sentencing memorandum regarding U.S. v. Feldman, 1989-1990 (Box 781, Folder 7)
      - S & L fraud: Thornburgh testimony: Hearing on Problems of the Federal Savings and Loan Insurance Corporation, Committee on Housing, Banking and Urban Affairs, U.S. Senate, February 9, 1989 (Box 781, Folder 8)
      - S & L fraud: "White Collar Crime," drafts of address by AG Thornburgh to the Federal Bar Association's Tom C. Clark Award luncheon, August 25, 1989 (Box 781, Folder 9)
      - S & L fraud: white collar crime news releases, reports and news clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 781, Folder 10)
      - "The Soviet Union and the Rule of Law," by AG Thornburgh, Foreign Affairs, Vol. 69, No. 2, Spring, 1990 (Box 781, Folder 11)
      - Supreme Court case: Payne v. Tennessee, argued by Thornburgh, 1991 (Box 781, Folder 12)
      - Supreme Court case: U.S. v. Pennsylvania Industrial Chemical Corporation, AG Thornburgh's request for information from case he argued as U.S. Attorney, April 30, 1990 (Box 781, Folder 13)
      - Quotes by Herbert Brownell, former Attorney General, and from speeches, articles and testimony by others, 1987-1991 (Box 781, Folder 14-15)
    - Telephone Logs and Messages
      - Telephone message forms, September 8, 1988-June 5, 1991 (Box 782, Folder 1-2)
      - Telephone logs, notes, messages and talking points, 1988-1991 (Box 782, Folder 3-5)
      - Department of Justice Daily Record of telephone communications made and received by Attorney General Dick Thornburgh, September 19, 1988-August 14, 1991 (Box 782, Folder 6-7)
  - Daily Schedules, 6.
    During the years that Dick Thornburgh was Attorney General his schedule was dense and fast-moving as is evident in these files. The schedules cover August 26, 1988 through August 15, 1991, and are chronologically arranged. The material includes Thornburgh's daily schedule while in Washington, as well as day trips made, and events he attended both locally and out of town The schedules include detailed information such as, for example: the persons met with, speech titles, others who accompanied him to events, and participants in the meetings that took place. There are a few items on the schedules that familiarly occurred each day, such as the morning meetings with his close advisors. These schedules allow the researcher to have a clear picture of the challenges each day presented.
    Included in this section are some Ginny Thornburgh daily schedules with dates ranging from January 12,1990 through May 21, 1991.
    It should be noted that foreign trips files and related schedules are in a separate section by that name.
    - Attorney General Thornburgh, August, 1988-August, 1990 (Box 783, Folder 1-13)
    - Attorney General Thornburgh, September, 1990-August, 1991 (Box 784, Folder 1-5)
    - Ginny Thornburgh, 1990-1991 (Box 784, Folder 6-11)
  - Events, 7.
    The event files of the Attorney General of the United States were maintained by the Attorney General's staff from August 1988 when Dick Thornburgh assumed office until he resigned in 1991 to seek the U.S. Senate seat in Pennsylvania. Thornburgh's priorities were clear from the start: to launch a "vigorous assault on drug trafficking," to continue to "focus on organized and white-collar crime" and to "step up activity in the civil rights, antitrust and environmental fields" (Evidence, p.208). The events in these files are extensive and well represent the follow-up actions related to those priorities, and other issues of note. Included, for example, are: white collar crime conferences, symposia, appearances before House and Senate Committees, Supreme Court case arguments, individual meetings, organization events at which he spoke, meetings around the country with U.S. Attorneys, law review banquets, briefings, civil rights meetings, receptions, and gold medal award banquet. They occurred both in and out of Washington, although international trips are in a separate section of the archive.
    The files are divided into the following five sections: 1) General Events, alphabetically ordered. Files contain both meetings with people and organizations, but also issues such as "Civil Rights Act" that include extensive background information; 2) International Events, alphabetically ordered. Files are principally events in which international figures visited Thornburgh in Washington D.C. Some files contain background about a related country, Mexico or the Philippines, for example; 3) Congressional Events, alphabetically ordered. These are events specifically relating to Thornburgh's meetings with members of the Congress of the United States. Some of the files are not events, but relate to topics such as: Crime Bills and Civil Rights Act, for example; 4) Press Events, alphabetically ordered. These are events relating to Thornburgh's interactions with the media: television, print, and radio. Here there also are articles written about the Attorney General or about a topic of note; and 5) Out-of-DC trips, alphabetically arranged by state.
    - General Events
      - ABA (American Bar Association) Annual Meeting, Chicago, IL, August 6, 1990 (Box 785, Folder 1)
      - ABA Commission on Minorities (Hayeck, Archer and Richie), Washington, DC, February 18, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 2)
      - ABA Federal Legal Executives Forum Luncheon, Washington, DC, June 29, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 3)
      - ABA House of Delegates Meeting, Honolulu, HI, August 8, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 4)
      - ABA House of Delegates, Pennsylvania Delegation, Honolulu, HI, August 8, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 5)
      - ABA Committee on the Federal Judiciary, Denver, CO, February 4, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 6)
      - ABA Committee on the Federal Judiciary, meeting with Ralph Lancaster, Washington, DC, August 23, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 7)
      - ABA Committee on the Federal Judiciary, meeting with Judge Harold Tyler, Washington, DC, April 4, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 8)
      - Abell, Rick (OJP), farewell ceremony, Washington, DC, August 2, 1990 (Box 785, Folder 9)
      - Abernathy, Reverend Ralph, Southern Christian Leadership Conference, Washington, DC, February 28, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 10)
      - Abraham, Lynne, District Attorney of Philadelphia, Washington, DC, June 24, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 11)
      - Abrams, Floyd, Washington, DC, December 20, 1990 (Box 785, Folder 12)
      - Abrams, Robert, Attorney General of New York, December 13, 1988 (Box 785, Folder 13)
      - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act), Public Hearing, Washington, DC, March 13, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 14)
      - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act), White House Signing Ceremony, Washington, DC, July 26, 1990 (Box 785, Folder 15)
      - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act), Regulations Status Report, Washington, DC, June 20, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 16)
      - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act), Regulations Signing, Washington, DC, July 17, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 17)
      - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act), First Anniversary Rose Garden Ceremony, Washington, DC, July 26, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 18)
      - ADA (Americans with Disabilities Act), Department of Justice First Anniversary Ceremony, Washington, DC, July 26, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 19)
      - Ad Hoc Group Against Crime, Kansas City, MO, January 23, 1990 (Box 785, Folder 20)
      - Adams, Judge Arlin, HUD Independent Counsel, Washington, DC, undated (Box 785, Folder 21)
      - Administrative Conference of the United States, Washington, DC, September 16, 1988 (Box 785, Folder 22)
      - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, Washington, DC, September 29, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 23)
      - African-American History Month, DOJ Observance, Washington, DC, February 21, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 24)
      - Agopian, Michael, Bureau of Justice Statistics (BJS), Washington, DC, June 14, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 25)
      - Agudath Israel of America, White House Briefing, Washington, DC, September 14, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 26)
      - Agudath Israel of America, 69th Annual Meeting, New York, NY, May 12, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 27)
      - Airline Industry Competition Issues, Antitrust Division, Washington, DC, January 9, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 28)
      - Alabama Legislature Joint Session, Montgomery, AL, May 2, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 29)
      - Alexander, Lamar, Reception, Washington, DC, April 16, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 30)
      - Alfalfa Club Dinner, Washington, DC, January 28, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 31)
      - Allison, Graham, Washington, DC, October 5, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 32)
      - All-Saints Episcopal School, May 5, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 33)
      - All-Star Game, Chicago, IL, July 10, 1990 (Box 785, Folder 34)
      - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, Pittsburgh, PA, November 14, 1988 (Box 785, Folder 35)
      - American Bankers Association, Conference on Money Laundering, New York, NY, October 26, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 36)
      - American Correctional Association, Annual Meeting, Baltimore, MD, August 14, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 37)
      - American Immigration Lawyers Association, Meeting, Washington, DC, July 24, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 38)
      - American Jewish Committee, Meeting, Washington, DC, July 31, 1990 (Box 785, Folder 39)
      - American Judicature Society, Luncheon, Denver, CO, February 4, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 40)
      - American Law Institute, Luncheon, Washington, DC, May 19, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 41)
      - American Legion, Pennsylvania Department Meeting, Pittsburgh, PA, July 12, 1989 (Box 785, Folder 42)
      - American Legislative Exchange Council, White House Briefings, Washington, DC, April 27, 1990, March 1, 1991 (Box 785, Folder 43)
      - American Legislative Exchange Council, Annual Conference, Boston, MA, July 27, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 1)
      - American Stock Exchange, Washington briefing, Washington, DC, October 15, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 2)
      - Andrews, Julie Rae, January 23, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 3)
      - Annenberg, Ambassador and Mrs. Walter, PA, May 16, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 4)
      - Anti-Defamation League, Meeting with David Brody, Washington, DC, January 3, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 5)
      - Anti-Defamation League, Civil Rights Committee Dinner, Philadelphia, PA, November 2, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 6)
      - Anti-Defamation League, White House Briefing, Washington, DC, March 14, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 7)
      - Antitrust Division, Brown Bag Lunch, Washington, DC, January 12, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 8)
      - Antitrust Division, Coffee, Washington, DC, January 30, 1991 (Box 786, Folder 9)
      - Antitrust Division, Enforcement Guidelines for International Operations, November 14, 1988 (Box 786, Folder 10)
      - Appeal of Conscience Foundation Annual Awards Dinner, New York, NY, October 18, 1988 (Box 786, Folder 11)
      - Arrington, Mayor Richard of Birmingham, June 29, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 12)
      - Ashcroft, John, Governor of Missouri, Washington, DC, February 20, 1991 (Box 786, Folder 13)
      - Asian-American Delegation, Family Reunification, Washington, DC, July 18, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 14)
      - Asian-Pacific Heritage Week, DOJ Commemoration, Washington, DC, May 9, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 15)
      - Asset Forfeiture Briefing, Washington, DC, March 15, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 16)
      - Asset Forfeiture Training Program Taping, Washington, DC, May 29, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 17)
      - Assistant Attorneys General, Washington, DC, August 16, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 18)
      - Associate Attorney General's Office, Washington, DC, November 10, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 19)
      - Association for Retarded Citizens (ARC), Annual Convention, Tampa, FL, November 8, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 20)
      - Association of American Publishers and American Booksellers Association, Meeting on Rushdie Threats, Washington, DC, March 1, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 21)
      - Association of General Counsels, Annual Fall Meeting, Washington, DC, October 12, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 22)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys, undated (Box 786, Folder 23)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys, Interview with Nancy Allen on AGAC History, Washington, DC, December 20, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 24)
      - Attorney General's Advisory Committee of U.S. Attorneys, Subcommittee on Child Pornography, Organized Crime, and Obscenity, Washington, DC, September 21, 1988 (Box 786, Folder 25)
      - Attorney General's Advocacy Institute, Washington, DC, March 29, 1990 (Box 786, Folder 26)
      - Attorney General's Award Ceremony, Washington, DC, March 8, 1991 (Box 786, Folder 27)
      - Attorney General's Birthday Party, Washington, DC, July 16, 1989, July 16, 1990, July 16, 1991 (Box 786, Folder 28)
      - Attorney General's Executive Staff Luncheon, Washington, DC, November 4, 1988 (Box 786, Folder 29)
      - Attorney General's Farewell Reception, Washington, DC, August 15, 1991 (Box 786, Folder 30)
      - Attorney General's Farewell Speech, Washington, DC, August 15, 1991 (Box 786, Folder 31)
      - Attorney General's Honor Program Recipient's Reception, Washington, DC, December 14, 1988 (Box 786, Folder 32)
      - Attorney General's Speech to DOJ Employees, Washington, DC, October 7, 1988 (Box 786, Folder 33)
      - Attorney General's Working Group on Reducing Violence in America, Arlington, VA, July 12, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 34)
      - Attorney Recruitment and Retention Study, Washington, DC, November 6, 1989 (Box 786, Folder 35)
      - Atwater, Lee, Funeral Service, Columbia, SC, April 1, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 1)
      - Ayer, Donald, Civil Rights Division Lunch, Washington, DC, November 27, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 2)
      - Ayer, Donald, Deputy Attorney General Swearing-in, Washington, DC, November 9, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 3)
      - Ayer, Donald, Deputy Solicitor General Farewell, Washington, DC, January 11, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 4)
      - Bank America, Dinner hosted by A.W. Clausen, Washington, DC, September 25, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 5)
      - Bank Fraud Working Group, December 15, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 6)
      - Barnette, Hank, Chairman of Bethlehem Steel, May 31, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 7)
      - Barr, Bill, Swearing-in Ceremony, Washington, DC, August 6, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 8)
      - Barr, Hank, U.S. District Courthouse, Scranton, PA, February 5, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 9)
      - Bartlett, Bo, Exhibition at P.P.O.W. Gallery, New York, NY, December 10, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 10)
      - Batavia, Andrew, Office of the Attorney General (OAG), Washington, DC, June 25, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 11)
      - Bates, David, Cabinet Secretary, Farewell reception, Washington, DC, May 29, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 12)
      - Bayh, Senator and Mrs., Dinner, Washington, DC, July 26, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 13)
      - Baylor University Scholars, Photo-op, Washington, DC, June 21, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 14)
      - Benkard, James, Washington, DC, August 1, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 15)
      - Bennett, Robert, Cleveland, OH, May 11, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 16)
      - Bennett, William, Director, Office of National Drug Control Policy, Washington, DC, March 13, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 17)
      - Bennett, William, Secretary of Education, Drug Education Discussion, Washington, DC, September 6, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 18)
      - Berman, Mike, Washington, DC, October 22, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 19)
      - Bloch Case, Washington, DC, February 15, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 20)
      - Bloch, Bob (Antitrust Division), Washington, DC, July 25, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 21)
      - Bloom, George, Funeral, Harrisburg, PA, February 5, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 22)
      - Blumstein, Alfred, Dean of the School of Public and Urban Affairs, Carnegie Mellon University, Washington, DC, March 29, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 23)
      - Boggs, Mr. and Mrs. Phillip, Washington, DC, October 21, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 24)
      - Bohlmann, Dr. Ralph, Missouri Synod Lutheran Church, Washington, DC, August 14, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 25)
      - Bolton, John (Civil Division), Farewell reception, Washington, DC, May 26, 1989 (Box 787, Folder 26)
      - Bonner, Judge, Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA) Swearing-in Ceremony, Arlington, VA, April 16, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 27)
      - de Borchgrave, Mr. and Mrs. Arnaud, Dinner, Washington, DC, October 26, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 28)
      - Bork, Robert, U.S. Court of Appeals, DC Circuit, Washington, DC, November 14, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 29)
      - Boskin, Michael, Council of Economic Advisers (CEA) Chairman, Washington, DC, February 26, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 30)
      - Boston Center for Independent Living (Americans with Disabilities Act, ADA), Boston, MA, September 14, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 31)
      - Bowen, Otis, Secretary of Health and Human Services, Washington, DC, September 21, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 32)
      - Bowsher, Charles, Comptroller General, Washington, DC, January 12, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 33)
      - Boys Club of America, Board of Directors, Washington, DC, September 27, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 34)
      - Brady, James, HBO Movie Premiere, Washington, DC, June 13, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 35)
      - Brady, Nicholas, Secretary of the Treasury, bank mergers, Washington, DC, February 8, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 36)
      - Brady, Nicholas, Secretary of the Treasury, luncheon, Washington, DC, October 28, 1988 (Box 787, Folder 37)
      - Brand, Judith, Supreme Court Admission Ceremony, Washington, DC, May 20, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 38)
      - Branstad, Terry, Governor of Iowa, Breakfast, Des Moines, IA, February 8, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 39)
      - Bravo, Ken, Washington, DC, June 17, 1991 (Box 787, Folder 40)
      - Breeden, Richard, Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) Chairman, Washington, DC, May 29, 1990 (Box 787, Folder 41)